<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AC TimeAttack</string>
    <string name="empty_list_view_description">Empty list view background image</string>

    <!-- Preferences -->
    <string name="pref_sound_key">pref_sound_key</string>

    <string name="pref_ip_key">pref_ip_key</string>
    <string name="pref_ip_title">IP address</string>
    <string name="pref_ip_summary">Your PS4\'s IP address from
        Settings/Network/View Connection Status/IP address</string>
    <string name="pref_ip_default">192.168.1.100</string>

    <string name="pref_udp_key">pref_udp_key</string>
    <string name="pref_udp_title">UDP rate</string>
    <string name="pref_udp_summary">Newer devices should use lower rate value for better
        synchronization. Default value is 15. Range is [10, 50]</string>
    <string name="pref_udp_default">15</string>

    <!-- Backup/Restore -->
    <string name="backup_ok">Backup completed successfully.</string>
    <string name="backup_fail">Error: backup failed.</string>
    <string name="restore_ok">Restore completed successfully.</string>
    <string name="restore_fail">Error: restore failed.</string>
    <string name="restore_warning">WARNING: \n\nRestoring laptimes from file will remove
        all your current laptimes in the database.\n\nAre you sure you want to continue?</string>

    <!-- DBActivity -->
    <string name="allow_access">Allow access to storage to be able to restore/backup laptimes.</string>

    <string
        name="about"><![CDATA[<h3>About Assetto Corsa</h3>Assetto Corsa is a sim racing video game developed
        by Kunos Simulazioni. It is designed with an emphasis on a realistic racing experience.<br><br/>
        <b>AC TimeAttack</b> is a companion app that aims to enhance the single player
        experience for console users. It saves your fastest laptimes for each car and track combination.</p>]]>
    </string>

    <string
        name="help"><![CDATA[<h2>Welcome to AC Time Attack!</h2><p>This app is a conversion of my pCARS for Project
        Cars app to Assetto Corsa. It displays timing information and stores your fastest laptimes for all car/track
        combinations in a database.

        <h3>Instructions</h3><p>Find out your PS4\'s IP address in the console\'s
        menu (Settings/Network/View Connection Status/IP address). Enter the IP address in the app\'s settings menu.
        Enable the WiFi on your device and restart the app by pressing
        the RESET APP button. Assetto Corsa will automatically communicate with the app once you start driving.</p>

        <h3>API Limitations</h3>
        The API developed by Kunos for the consoles is a limited version of the one available for PC and
         some of its features are missing. For instance, the API does not tell about the layout selected by the user
         in the game. For instance, the API sees both Barcelona GP and Barcelona Moto as just Barcelona. My workaround
         this problem is to display a menu with the different layouts for the selected track before starting recording
         data. A pop up menu will appear after every reset for those tracks with more than one layout.

        <h3>Database</h3>
        The database storing the laptimes can be accessed via the <b>Edit Database</b> option in the menu. Individual
        laptimes can be deleted and the entire database can be backed up as a JSON file with path Downloads/actimeattack/data
        in your Android device.

        <h3>Important</h3>
        Please remember to backup your database before removing/reinstalling AC Time Attack. The database with
        all its data is part of the app. If you want to reinstall the app or move your laptimes to another
         device use the backup/restore options in the menu.

        <h3>Problems running AC Time Attack?</h3>
        1. Make sure your WiFi is on and connected to the same
        network as your game console.<br/><br/>2. If you are using an older or slower Android device and you are
        having problems try changing the UDP rate in the settings menu. This will introduce a slight delay in the communication
        but might solve your problem.

        <h3>Reset App button</h3>
        Assetto Corsa does not inform the app about changes in car/track configuration. The reset app button
        forces the game to share that information so the app can update itself and record data for the right car/track combo.

        <h3>The on/off button</h3>
        This is a toggle button with two states. This button pauses the communication between
        the game and the app. It is useful for instance when watching replays.
        Press the button before entering replay to avoid recording corrupted data and press again when resuming driving.</p>]]>
    </string>

</resources>
